all right Sarah has a bone to pick with
her friend of me uh Sierra what's going
on my ex-roommate slash I guess ex-best
friend yeah and I are having a dispute
over my dog she's not giving me
visitation rights to him
and wait over your dog yes we have like
basically a child together you and your
roommate uh X roommate extra oh I see so
when you were roommates you had the dog
yes that's what we potentially got for
and so how did you break up I mean how
did you she just left or well we were
roommates and
she ended up you know like like we were
together you know best friends and all
sharing a room and she ended up starting
to escort
slash being a stripper and so I ended up
kicking her out because I mean there was
just too many guys in and out and I got
tired of it so you said you're out of
here but the dog went to yes one day
when I was at work she ended up leaving
taking the dog taking the bed taking a
bunch of our accessories that we had
together that I also invested into I see
and it's I just want to see my dog so
you don't care you're not trying to get
her back to roommate no I just I want my
child you want your dog I don't want my
child oh at least oh there's the door oh
yeah is that a uh female or maybe it's a
boy his name's Keela wouldn't be the
first time we had a [__] on the show
[Applause]
no it's a it's a male girl
and it's just like you know I just want
visitation rights or I want my dog or
either she's just gonna get her ass
kicked yeah oh
it's a child you can't mess with my
child and what's her name not the dog or
her
Kindle here's Kendall
no
heels off hi
so are you gonna give me my visitations
right to my dog back or what oh my dog
no my dog the one that's the one I gave
you a ride to to go get the dog who's
paid for his butt bills and his food I
took you there did you train when you
were being a stripper in an escort they
were you were doing all the nights I was
at work and you were at home with him
and I was always taking care of him I
was always walking yeah I was always
doing everything so when you were
working at the club too who do you think
was taking care of him hey you're being
a stripper showing your ass showing all
that while I was only a cocktail
waitress fully clothed so who made more
money doing that uh obviously right
that's why I could afford to take care
of our dogs obviously not because look
who got kicked out yeah and took him
with me and still he's living a way
better life than he was with you anytime
you have
the only time that my dog had an
accident was when he was left with you
unattended oh does he drive and how many
times
I wish because then maybe he could
actually make the effort to go see his
other parent because she doesn't so I've
been trying to text you how many times
you've texted me one time and said that
you were gonna come see him because you
had one of your boy toys
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
if you think you're mad about the dog
wait till I tell you about me and your
man at lights all night
[Applause]
you slept with a boyfriend you're saying
I don't think they were dating she's got
multiple boyfriends but
[Applause]
oh
yeah how did that happen
well we were at lights all night
um
thank you yeah keep going okay and the
second night I had Brandon to him he
looked so cute he had a man bun
everything
[Applause]
he thought I looked pretty nice in mind
and that's why you're a [__] oh cause
he and that's why you're still a dirty
horse you should be worried about that
you wanted me instead of you that night
you're a dirty [__] anybody loves me
could you hook up with anybody ah
sweetie that's you shaking your ass for
everybody
yeah
[Applause]
so hi how's everybody doing
all right nice to see you again
yeah
oh man
man all right so uh how long have
YouTube been going together
five six months maybe yeah not too long
you know just figuring stuff out yeah
and she helped you figure it out a
couple things yes
what do you want to say to him
your dirty [__] just like her
I did what I had to do I'm sorry she
just looks so nice and you were I'm sure
it does anything looks nice to you you
think with you not your head
well maybe if you were alone that's why
we're not official and maybe if you were
a little more available
maybe she wouldn't curb me so much I
wouldn't have to look for affection
somewhere else
major affection I don't care about you
get away from
away from who's Gracie
oh your best friend to step the hell
away from me
you can go be with that horse crazy
[Applause]
[Music]
hi Jerry hi Gracie
um yeah how do you figure into you guys
are friends yeah
and what do you add to the story okay so
I'm here because of this girl screw all
these people
um well that's happened already yeah
yeah
okay so this is my best friend and I'm
actually here to tell her something oh
well
I want her to move
past everything I think she's so sexy
her hair is so sexy her body's sexy like
look at this girl like seriously
[Applause]
I'm here oh I also want to get my first
kiss today my lesbian kiss because
[Applause]
[Music]
we'll be back
this is a strange story as I understand
it you've been texting this guy or
so I'm actually here today to meet this
guy named Brian we've had online
relationships for seven months yeah and
I'm here to meet him for the first time
you know like our relationship started
on Facebook yeah he inboxed me and like
I tried to like give him to video chat
me because I didn't want him to seem
fake and when he did aside from there we
just went off like we've been taught we
started texting every day talking every
day and we were supposed to just you
know remain friends until we actually
decided to meet because he lives in
Atlanta and I live in Texas and he's
told you that he has a girlfriend
well you you can't tell who did you
contact
well
um what happened was so one day I was
talking to Brian and he made this
Facebook post about me saying like I'm
his woman crush and basically telling
everyone how in love he is with me oh
okay and you know there was a bunch of
comments on it like oh she's so perfect
y'all make a perfect couple and then
this one comment with this girl named
Alexis on it like
um her comment said is this for real
like she seemed shocked and then she
inboxed me and she was like is this for
real and I was like why are you coming
at me like I should be coming at you
like why are you asking me this and she
was like I've been dating Brian for a
while and I was just like what's a while
I've been with him seven months and
she's like I've been with him longer and
I was just like okay and then she
started saying things like I'm his first
love and then like children got involved
but they're not his but they call him
dad and things like that and it just
really just took me to a point where I
just went off and so I made this post
yeah because he gave me his Facebook yep
and so I was just like basically I was
like so and what does this say
um when I was
when I was going to log out of his stuff
this morning I saw that yet another girl
that texted him and guess what she calls
him husband
oh yeah I'm just letting you know the
man isn't faithful until he want to make
all of us look stupid he about to look
stupid as
well there must be another word there
don't play with me below is a picture of
me I won't post the other girls but this
is me and I wrote this post trust me I
regret nothing so you are getting
information
that there's other women involved yes
like Alexis was one of the main girls
that's been with him the longest yeah
and so why so my question to you is
since you've never even met him why
would you even want to start a
relationship if you know he's got
another woman in his life who could be
his wife well that's like he's not
really they're not really married yeah
like it's just like wife like wifey it's
like a nickname type thing okay but
there let's assume they have a
relationship yeah but like it's just the
point of
with this guy
they're really met him no and you're
going to meet him now yes
okay his name is Brian here you're going
to meet him now here's Brian
foreign
each other seen videos
Etc yeah so you knew
you were going to get to meet yeah yeah
but what do you want to say to her
what I want to say about me is I'm sorry
for everything that I did to you I'm
sorry for hurting you and sorry for
bringing you on this mess and I didn't
mean for none of this to happen
for what to happen
to play with so hard like that and put
you in the situation where there's
another woman
[Music]
I brought you on the show because I
wanted to confess how I felt about you
um
I still have even though we broke off or
whatever I still have a lot of feelings
for you and my love for you is still
there it's never like weakened it's
never a weekend in any type of way it's
just like the trust Factor did but that
can be built and so I'm asking you kind
of I guess I'm asking you if you would
be willing
to try to maybe work things out
I would honestly like to say yes I would
like to build a few and make it
offensive
and even though you have a girlfriend
honestly yes for how from six years back
and forth on it on and off yeah
wow okay well let's bring around let's
bring her out again here's Alexis
[Applause]
you're the one looking stupid bro I look
stupid because you love my man you've
never seen him before are you getting it
you can't talk
[Applause]
[Music]
so what time
who does that nobody obviously
girl I graduated this year I can easily
come here
you think you're an adult when you
graduate
scholarships to basketball
are you any good
on any good okay am I any good what what
do you what do you want to say to him
so you gonna try with her
huh
this is the person I've been wanting to
meet since oh me day one honestly meat
and be with this person honestly
when are you gonna see her
I was gonna make time to see her oh
she's gonna make time to see her but you
but you sit here you say you want to
marry me you want to be with me
we've been together for six years you
want to have a family with me what what
have we been trying to do yeah we'll see
what have we been trying to do oh it's
sad okay if you say something you need
to be truthful it don't need to be a lot
I understand that
but at the same time when I met
Dominique she showed me something way
different from you
message
phone call I wasn't even a phone call
FaceTime not a FaceTime okay then you
have not seen her what is she showing
you if you have not seen you say I'm
showing him something better because
you're there
[Applause]
[Music]
is there a problem yeah there's a
problem oh yeah it is a problem the
problem is you because obviously
[Applause]
every day he wants me I'm there for him
that's me he don't want you bro
he's just talking he's not going nowhere
oh he's not no he's not oh okay because
he already came before he is not going
nowhere
[Applause]
so you're saying you want to leave her
honestly uh
[Applause]
wow what did I do
Rush relationships instead of taking
time and building slow
you want to rush marriage you want to
rush a kid we're nothing but 20
something years old we've been together
for six years since high school high
school sweethearts dude
you went everywhere with me I walked to
your house
to be with you
are you serious
and there and there's nothing that I can
give you are you serious you you love my
kids bro you you call my you call my
child your princess you let her call you
Daddy
are you serious and you gonna leave me
for that
what gives you the right
what I can say to you also is sorry for
wasting your time forget you sorry bro
[Applause]
are you worried that seeing what he
would do to her after six years that
he'll he's going to turn around at some
point and do that to you I mean it is a
concern that's what I'm saying like
like my trusted so like before we get
together I would like to just take it
slow at first and just be friends at
first you know just work something
towards it but if I know that me and him
is going to talk and possibly be
together again then there's doesn't need
to be another person like
and you want to be with her
I want to be with Dominique
what
[Music]
are you kidding me
she's a kid bro you're 22.
you've been with me we've been together
for this entire time but we have points
where we were on and off that was
because of you because you wanted to
dump me to go be with some other girl
every time I didn't do nothing but love
you and cherish every moment with you
even the ones we didn't even do nothing
but sit and talk the little things
matter
[Applause]
just to look at you matters bro just to
smell you when I get a chance bro give
you a hug when I hug you there's nothing
else there I feel like I'm floating okay
when you kiss me I feel like there's
nothing that could hurt me when you
stand next to me when you see my kids
my kids mean the world to me for you to
hurt them now what I'm gonna tell them
to say on that
because you never know you always say oh
no we'll be back
Serena is not falling for romantic
proposal from her man please welcome
Serena to the show
hi Serena
what is this oh marry me it says yeah
yeah you guys see this beautiful
proposal right here yeah it was supposed
to be a happy day yeah yeah well it's
not going to be why not you see
I just found out that my man's cheated
on me with some nasty [__] hoe
a nasty [__] hoe yes and how do you know
that I mean it on you oh I'm gonna tell
you how see this morning when I was
taking my break I was going out for my
morning cigarette walking down the hall
and I see Dede now being here at the
studio no Dede my co-worker here at the
studio why is she here when this is
supposed to be a proposal right no I'm
gonna tell you Didi Didi is just a
regular schmegular hoe
that's where I draw the line yeah
Dede is the type of woman or the type of
female that you always
walking around wrapping her legs around
every other woman's mans oh and I don't
like but how long you've been with your
boyfriend who's gonna apparently
proposing to you here so I have been
with my boyfriend for five years or I
was with him for five years I kicked him
out about a month and a half ago oh okay
so you're not living with him anymore no
Jerry we have our own we have our own
issues trust me so when he's coming here
on the show to say marry me you're not
ready for that you want to know what I
think about his
this is what I
said
[Applause]
so you think he's messing around with
with this other woman oh absolutely
absolutely I know he is because when I
saw her and I walked towards her yeah
this morning when I saw her walk towards
her yeah as soon as she saw me this girl
ran the opposite way booked it down the
hall immediately when I saw that girl
running I was like I just put two and
two together why is Didi this regular
hoe here first of all why is my man's
here yeah okay
I'm not dumb obviously this whole my man
oh yeah
okay well Adrian's your boyfriend look
he wants to apparently he wants to
propose because it was his idea to put
this marry me thing here so let's bring
him out here's Adrian
well you know that I'm here to propose
to you I sure do I sure do
you want to know what Adrian I'm so sick
of you I'm done with this I can't I
can't I can't continuously be unheard
unlistened to
not taken care of so not focus on I
don't see how they how you can put two
and two together like that I've always
been here for you no no no everything
that I possibly can to make sure that
and ensure that you're happy as a woman
and what do I get back in return
I get called that I'm a punk ass I'm a
[__] I get told all kinds of things
that are just degrading to a man she
never called you
oh I heard the schmagula before Jerry
yeah we that's that's the thing that's
that's an ongoing thing
you want to know Adrian I'm gonna tell
you how I really feel about you you want
to know what I never loved you
look at you right now
I don't even like you and I'm sick of
being let down but you've been with him
for five years oh I was with him for
five years
that was has this cheating been an
ongoing thing no it was the first time
and it's it's it was the first time that
anything like that has ever happened in
our relationship we ain't never had no
kind of drama like that in our
relationship it's just feeling like she
don't care about me like she's ready to
move on she's lost all this weight she
lost 50 pounds and now all of a sudden
she's now all of a sudden she's just
[Applause]
feeling like she's better than feeling
like she's better than me is how I feel
like that's where you're wrong Adrian I
never changed up I changed for the
better okay what I did stop was I
stopped needing to be validated by
people and that people is you and people
like schmegular DD okay and that's why
I'm done I can't well that's me
[Applause]
foreign
after everything I've been done seeing
what you done you know my situation I
work with you we're friends
How You Gonna sleep with him
just because we worked together that
only we're friends you wanna know a
[__]
[Applause]
you knew they were together right yes
yeah but I don't care but you you don't
care do you want to be with him do you
no I just haven't had sex in a while and
he was just there
well it was a one-time thing how did it
come about
it all came about I mean I know what
here's what it was I'm at the gym right
yeah and I'm doing my workout I'm coming
towards the end of my workout yeah like
a little cool down kind of thing so I'm
doing my push-ups and stuff and I see I
I know I'm seeing this girl staring at
me I'm just knowing that I recognize her
kind of and then she comes up to me she
starts doing her squats and her lunges
right in front of me like ass all out
right in my face doing her thing okay
okay
so I'm knowing that and then I put two
and T together this is this you know
this is this is deedy this is the girl
that I've seen with Serena and so
therefore you said oh
[Applause]
go back to regula
yeah at that at that point in time
um Jerry I wasn't I wasn't thinking
right it was just uh she was there okay
but there's no relationship here she's
not interested you're not interested no
no Jerry it was like I said a one-time
kind of thing so what's gonna happen
here because you do love her well you
asked her to marry you I'm assuming you
love her I do love her yeah it's what I
think of your
cool
that's typical
we'll be back
all right Mia says she's excited to meet
her online crush and he will see her as
well in the flesh you've never met him
before right no oh so how did you get in
touch with him over
um he messaged me on Facebook and we've
been talking for about six to seven
months now and everything was
pretty casual and then it turned into
more once he found out that I'm a
stripper oh
oh
my God
so but when he first
showed interest in you he didn't know
you were stripper yeah it was very
casual just like friendly type oh I see
and then you let him know and then he
became even more interested but yeah
because he's never been to a strip club
or even known any strippers
I told you he never was at a strip club
yeah and you believed him
he seems like it yeah
uh and he seems like a nice guy
apparently yes yeah and so you've
arranged to meet him here today yes okay
well good and uh tell me something about
him uh well he's from Texas yeah he
rides bulls and like varieties yeah and
I don't know anyone who does that so I
thought that was interesting
wow yeah
until you're looking forward to meeting
him yes well good okay uh he's outside
the studio so he hasn't heard any of
this but here he is here's Austin
hmm
oh my God
I finally get to meet you nice to meet
you too
I know they just told me that Chris is
for your favorite
oh isn't that nice thing
[Applause]
so uh hey Austin so you found out she
was a stripper did that increase your
interest well yeah yeah I have never
been at this trip you've never never
even met one you've never even met one
yeah okay and you've never been to a
strip club no really every day of my
life wow okay good deal and she said
that you ride bowls and yeah right boys
on weekends and stuff and during the
summer with my friends wow that's yeah
well what do you you just met so what do
you want to say to him
well when I come to Texas you offered
well I model and I do dance for a living
and I was asked to go to Texas so he
offered oh you asked her to come to
Texas no I offered let me stay with him
so I didn't have to stay at a hotel I
see what you're saying okay
and uh I offered to let her stay with me
and everything oh wow very nice and
you're going to stay with him now that
we've met possibility
you happy about that yeah all my friends
tell me it's pretty cool to have a yeah
they'll probably all come over to visit
yeah
they'll be waiting there when you you
come in there right and did you get
because he seems pretty shy like a
really nice guy I mean I'm shy too but
not that shy yeah
and you meet guys like this or are most
of the guys you meet guys that you know
know they're more dominant he's more you
think passive yes yeah a lot that's the
word that came to mind who's Roxanna
that's my girlfriend
[Applause]
you're you're not as shy as I thought
yeah
yeah well wait is it if you have a
girlfriend how is she going to come and
stay with you
I just know about it she doesn't know
about it oh boy well she's here she
she's backstage
you didn't know that he had a girlfriend
well here's Roxanna
[Applause]
hi
are you really moving her in with you if
she needed a place to stay
but we were supposed to move in together
we planned this how long have you guys
been together we've been together for 10
months
so you started talking to her right
after we got together
pretty close to it
some dirty prostitute
like why would you want that
why would you want some dirty [__]
it's a new experience
it's a new experience okay
I mean
sorry
it is
you don't really seem sorry well maybe
your relationship wasn't secure in the
first time you don't get to speak
trust me you're doing if these doesn't
have your just some used up washed up
little [__]
and you look like you're going to church
so oh really
[Applause]
oh look at that oh that's that's cute
your little your lipstick's kind of
messed up you might want to fix it oh
your face messed up
[Applause]
well it in fairness to her she didn't
know anything about you he's the one
that lied I mean I didn't know but I
didn't care now oh I see it doesn't
matter
so what are you gonna do are you dumping
me
yeah
did you tell her that you loved her
I have in the past yes
seem to marry me
Scott bored with it
how old are you 19 fixing me 20.
okay wait he's fixing to be 20.
how old are you
I just turned 18.
nobody thinks how he's treated you as
fair or good or nice but he's
19. so you have to take that into
account that a guy is 19 and says
whatever he says you got to take with a
grain of salt
because he's 19. he may not be committed
from that pardon we have so much more
than that what
talk to her
I feel like there was more thought so
every conversation we had it meant
nothing
not really
shouldn't even let her know
you could have told me in the beginning
all right Larissa says her boyfriend is
not following the Playbook
oh what's what's that about
well me and my boyfriend we recently
just moved in together we've been living
together for about a month now yeah and
um how's it going
not so good
um how long has he been your boyfriend
four years oh so it's a long-term it's
my high school sweetheart I got it so a
long-term relationship yeah yeah prom
and everything
it turns out yeah it's just not good we
well I actually moved away in a
relationship to Cincinnati for two years
so it was a long distance relationship
so it was actually hard yeah but once I
graduated high school from there
um
I we talked about moving together yes in
May and so we did move together and we
started going to college together in
Akron yes and um
it's just I don't know what's bad about
it he's a football player I always have
to help him like I always have to help
him out do his doing his homework and I
have to push him forward and he's just I
don't know he lies to me about little
things he um I'm not allowed to go out
with my friends I'm not allowed to do
anything so and I just feel like there's
been something going on with him so so
ever since you moved in together he
seems more distant yeah I see
the next name I have here is precious
precious
do you know precious
um yeah I went to high school with her
oh okay so she's a friend all right
here's your friend precious
[Applause]
you dumb [__]
what are you talking about what is this
what do you mean you've been replaced
[__]
[Applause]
I was replaced yes how I mean I've been
with him for four years well let's see
it started
over the summer I met him at Buffalo
Wings the Buffalo Wing Stop his favorite
place by the way
um we had a few beers we went back to
his car he fell on my thigh a little bit
oh really I hopped up on him
[Applause]
you're just a little hoe so I mean I'd
rather be at home than have a fake ass
relationship
I mean well um I'm sorry you're just
I'm just wet
you're dirty you're just really dirty
you're so dirty I have no words to say
to you you're just so if you guys were
friends why would you want to do that to
her because I don't care about her I
care about myself and when I want
something I'm gonna get it Jerry
okay well why don't we bring out Tony
[Applause]
why would you do this to me
I don't want to be with you anymore all
you do is cry about stuff you want to
follow me around everywhere I go I I
want new things and meet new people why
would you move me from Cincinnati all
the way to Akron if you didn't want to
be with me you want
you want in
you begged me every time you did
something wrong you begged me oh baby
please please move in with me I love you
I'm gonna marry you I want to be with
you
yes I did say those things but at the
time I thought it would help our
relationship yeah but now that we're
moved in together I don't feel like it's
helping it at all it's actually breaking
us apart
but you've been with it for four years
yeah I've been with her for four years
and now that we're living together we're
together constantly and constantly here
so when I get a chance to do something I
would like to go do it
um Jerry um
I'm trying out for the Akron football
team I I run a 4 9 40. I bench 300. okay
well that sounds that sounds really good
I'm not the coach so I can't
I can't but uh I'll put it I'll put in a
good word for you I don't know yeah uh
so uh but but this relationship here do
you love her
I do oh that was slow
yeah
not not as much as you did before or not
as much as I did before and what about
your relationship there with the
precious uh we don't have no
relationships it was just a one-time
thing she says
[Applause]
she was just a benchwarmer she's nothing
special to me at all
you weren't saying that when you were in
my legs
[Applause]
that's where you it wasn't the best
sick with little Miss Snow White shut up
[__]
to be with me I don't go for trash
anyways yeah but you got number one fan
on your shirt
oh because you liked when I you liked
when I did that real nice thing it
wasn't that good
okay
so so you go to his games or yes
I don't pay attention to her
would you invite me
not I don't always invite you usually
just pop up okay we'll play that game
okay are you saying this is over yes I'm
saying it's over oh yeah I don't want
nothing to do with him
we'll be back
if you think that was wild and crazy
then click here to keep watching and
don't forget to subscribe all you have
to do is click here and one more thing
take care of yourself and each other